{
    "subject": "resource/Neue_Staatsgalerie",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "The Neue Staatsgalerie in Stuttgart, Germany, was designed by the British firm James Stirling, Michael Wilford and Associates, although largely accredited solely to partner James Stirling.  It was constructed in the 1970s and opened to the public in 1984. The building has been claimed as the epitome of Post-modernism.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of the Neue Staatsgalerie in Stuttgart, Germany, is that it was designed by James Stirling, Michael Wilford and Associates.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9735265970230103,
            "question": "Is James Stirling associated with the design of the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9103732705116272,
            "question": "Who designed the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8865991234779358,
            "question": "Who are the architects credited with designing the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8437219858169556,
            "question": "Besides James Stirling, who else designed the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8153880834579468,
            "question": "In what country is the Neue Staatsgalerie situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7820936441421509,
            "question": "Where is the Neue Staatsgalerie located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7653933763504028,
            "question": "What architectural firm designed the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6993546485900879,
            "question": "Can you name a known architect who worked on the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6766241788864136,
            "question": "What type of building is the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6558593511581421,
            "question": "What is the name of the architectural firm that collaborated on the Neue Staatsgalerie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of the Neue Staatsgalerie in Stuttgart, Germany, is that it was designed by James Stirling, Michael Wilford and Associates.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6348_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of building is the Neue Staatsgalerie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6348_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a known architect who worked on the Neue Staatsgalerie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6348_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What architectural firm designed the Neue Staatsgalerie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6348_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6348_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that the Neue Staatsgalerie in Stuttgart, Germany, was designed by James Stirling, Michael Wilford and Associates (in multiple files)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the Neue Staatsgalerie in Stuttgart, Germany, was designed by the British firm James Stirling, Michael Wilford and Associates, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}